postcodez.com.au 2018-05-12

# Qpzm Australia

**Privacy Policy**

Twit Solutions Pty Ltd is committed to responsible privacy practices and to complying with the National Privacy Principles contained in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth). The following information details our Privacy Policy with respect to how and why we collect personal information from our web site and how this information is used. 

**Information collected through normal browsing of this site**  
In the course of normal web site usage Twit Solutions Pty Ltd collects the IP address, the referring web site URL and the date and time of file requests to which information is sent. This information is used as the basis of our statistic generation that measures activity within the site, which is in turn used for internal purposes to maintain and improve the quality of information that we display. 

We do not collect or store in the course of this usage information that identifies you as an individual, such as your name, email address, or other personal details. 

**Collection of other information**  
Within some pages of the Qpzm.com.au web site you are able to initiate a request for additional information or commence a dialogue with Twit Solutions Pty Ltd. This information is used and stored by Twit Solutions Pty Ltd only for the purposes of responding to this request and is never provided to any other company for that company's independent use. 

**Collection of information through shop.qpzm.com.au (QpzmShop)**  
Users who make a purchase from QpzmShop you will be required to provide information to us in order to fulfill the transaction. This information is used and stored by Twit Solutions Pty Ltd only for the purposes of processing the order transaction. Parts of this information are submitted to a secure 3rd party gateway for the purposes of approving payments. This information is only used to process payments and is not for that company's independent use. 

**Use of cookies**  
The Qpzm.com.au web site uses "cookies" to manage the display of information as you use the site. A cookie is a small data element stored by your web browser on your computer system. Cookies do not store your email address or other personal information about you. 

Qpzm will safeguard your personal information in accordance with any applicable Australian laws, judicial and legal orders, and as other uses necessary in order to protect the rights, property or safety of Qpzm, its users or others. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and would like to know your options in relation to not having this information used by these companies, **[click here](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html)**. 

If the business of Qpzm is sold, or transfers substantially all of its assets to a third party, any customer information retained by Qpzm is considered a business asset. Customer contact information and purchase histories may be transferred in connection with the sale for purposes of continuing the business. 

This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically. 

Copyright © 2012 Twit Solutions Pty Ltd.
